XtraWrkx LinkedIn Extension Icons

Required icon files:
- icon16.png (16x16 pixels) - Toolbar icon
- icon48.png (48x48 pixels) - Extension management page
- icon128.png (128x128 pixels) - Chrome Web Store

These should be PNG files with the XtraWrkx logo/branding.
Use the same orange gradient colors as the CRM (#ffaa44 to #ffcc66).

For now, you can create simple colored squares or use any placeholder icons.
The extension will work without these files, but Chrome will show default icons.